maxandchloe.com 2016-12-03

# Privacy Policy | Max & Chloe

Privacy Policy  
  
We respect your privacy. Our Privacy Statement is offered to inform you about our policies and the information that we collect from our website. Your use of our site represents your acceptance of our Privacy Statement and consent to its applications. We reserve the right to change our policy at any time.

**Information**  
We do not collect personal information about you unless you provide it. You can visit [www.maxandchloe.com](http://www.maxandchloe.com/) without revealing personally identifiable information.

We collect anonymous information during visits to our site. This includes the type of browser, server name, IP address, date and time you access our site, pages you access, and an internet address from which you linked, if any, to us. This is not personally identifiable.

Personally Identifiable Information identifies you and how we may contact you. This includes your name, address, telephone and fax number, social security number, email address or any information you voluntarily submitted to us. We can receive this information from you by email, telephone, in writing, or in person.

Max & Chloe collects personally identifiable information about you, as you choose, when you register with us for a purchase, promotion, or when opting-in to receive information through another website. This includes, but is not limited to, your name, email address, postal address, phone numbers, credit card information, interests, product use, purchases, birth date, gender, etc.

We may collect information about your transactions and other activity of yours on the site. This information may include, but is not limited to, areas of the website you visit, transactions, viewing content, downloads, payments, shipping, billing, and those with whom you correspond and communicate.

**Use**  
Max & Chloe uses personally identifiable information about you for internal purposes. This includes, but is not limited to, establishing your identity; servicing you; processing your transactions; upgrading the website to suite your needs; providing updates for your information, promotional notices, and other information about Max & Chloe and our affiliates; security and integrity.

We also use anonymous browsing information collected to manage and improve our website, for advertisers, potential business partners and other unaffiliated entities. This information is not personally identifiable.

Max & Chloe does not share your personally identifiable information with other organizations for their marketing to you. We may use unaffiliated companies to help us maintain and operate our website or other reasons to operate our business, and these organizations may receive your personally identifiable information. We may disclose personal information to satisfy government requests, legal requirements, and protect the rights and property of www.maxandchloe.com, users, and affiliates.

**Security**  
Max & Chloe maintains an advanced security system or Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to help protect your personal information. Information is transmitted to and from us in encrypted form. Please know that emails and other transmissions from you via the Internet cannot be completely protected against unauthorized interception.

**Cookies**  
Our server and the servers of companies that are used to operate this site, may place "cookies" on your computer depending on your browser and to allow full use of the website.

A "cookie" is a small file that may be stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow us to recognize your computer while you are on our website, personalize your experience, improve our site's functions, track transactions and maintain your information for future service. We are not responsible for advertisers or other providers that may appear on this website and use cookies that are not sent by us.

If you turn off your cookies, you may not be able to use certain personalized functions of our website. 

**Links**  
[www.maxandchloe.com](http://www.maxandchloe.com/) may link to other websites such as advertisers, retail partners, or content providers offering downloads on our site. We are not responsible for the content of other websites, and, they may use cookies. We suggest that you read the privacy policies of other websites before you offer personally identifiable information. 

**Children**  
We do not collect or solicit information from, approve applications for, or maintain accounts for any child knowingly under the age of 13. We must rely on the parents and guardians of those under 13 to decide on material for such children to view and authorize purchases.

**Communications**  
We may send you messages and updates about Max & Chloe, our affiliates, promotions, etc. If you prefer not to receive non-transaction information, please send us an email at [customerservice@maxandchloe.com](mailto:info@maxandchloe.com).

**Changes**  
If you would like to change, update, or delete your personal information at any time, please send us an email to [ customerservice@maxandchloe.com](mailto:info@maxandchloe.com).
